<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/main"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".ProgressActivity">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:background="#678">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:fontFamily="@font/courgette"
            android:text="Progress"
            android:textAlignment="center"
            android:textColor="#080C12"
            android:textSize="32sp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="280dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
            android:src="@drawable/image3"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/recipesText"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:fontFamily="@font/courgette"
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:text="I) Nutritional Milestones\n\n1.Hydration Streak: Number of consecutive days meeting a daily water goal (e.g., 8 glasses).\n\n2. Whole Food Ratio: Tracking the percentage of meals made from scratch vs. ultra-processed foods.
            \n\n3.Fiber Intake: Meeting daily targets for vegetables, fruits, and legumes to support gut health.\n\n4.Reduced Added Sugar: Tracking days without sodas, candies, or hidden sugars in processed snacks.\n\nII). Physical and Functional Wins\n\n1.Energy Levels: A daily 1–10 scale to track afternoon slumps vs. sustained energy.\n\n2.Sleep Quality: Hours of restful sleep; nutrition significantly impacts sleep cycles.\n\n3.Non-Scale Victories (NSVs): Qualitative wins like clothes fitting better,clearer skin, or stronger nails.\n\n4.Physical Stamina: Noting if daily tasks (like climbing stairs) feel easier due to better fueling.\n\nIII). Behavioral and Psychological Growth\n\n1.Mindful Eating: Tracking how often the user ate without distractions (no TV/phone).\n\n2.Hunger Cues: Success in stopping at 80% full rather than overeating.\n\n3.Meal Prep Consistency: Number of meals planned or prepped in advance to avoid emergency fast food.\n\n4.Mood Correlation: Noting the link between specific meals and emotional well-being.\n\nIV). Advanced Health Metrics \n\n1.Blood Sugar Stability: For those tracking data, noting fewer  shaky feelings between meals.\n\n2.Recovery Time: How quickly the body bounces back after exercise (fueled by proper protein/carbs)."
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textSize="16sp" />


    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>